winmaximizer.com 2011-05-30

# Privacy Policy - WinMaximizer

## Privacy Policy

Celeritas Software Company is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you may provide to us when using any of our online services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat information we receive when you transmit data to Celeritas Software Company.

#### Information Collection

When you purchase, download trial or evaluation versions, or register WinMaximizer software, we may collect personal information including your name, address, email address, etc. for the purpose of recording the transaction when you engage in activities on our web site or within the WinMaximizer software. When we use a payment processing merchant we ensure that the same strict privacy criteria are in place. We do not (knowingly) collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. We also give users the option of receiving useful product information (such as updates, pest alerts and associated product offerings), via opt-in permission based email. We fully ensure your privacy and value your trust. We will never sell, rent, lease, or give your information to a third party unless required to do so by law. You may opt out of receiving emails from us at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email or by visiting our website at www.WinMaximizer.com. By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to Celeritas Software Company's collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes as outlined herein.

Any information that you post to a chat room, public bulletin or forum is available to all users of that site. Celeritas Software Company cannot control, nor is it responsible for the use, disclosure, or dissemination of such information by any third parties. 

#### Web Site Usage

We may automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information when you access our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors navigate our sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors, length of visits, etc.

#### How Information Is Used When Collected 

We may use information collected in the following ways:

  * To process, validate and verify purchases.
  * To contact you to reconfirm or verify accuracy of information provided.
  * To register you as a customer.
  * To open and maintain a support account for you.
  * To send email notifications about new, existing, enhanced products or services.
  * To send information on special offers, or to obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or provide added products and services.
  * To enable us to personalize content, advertising and promotions based on preferences, needs, suggestions, or recommendations.
  * To provide advance notice of termination of a trial period or an opportunity to extend a trial period, or advance notice of expiration of your software license.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example protect our intellectual property rights), and your compliance with the applicable End User License Agreement(s) contained within the WinMaximizer software. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the applicable law may require us to do so.

#### Cookies

We define a cookie as any string of data and information that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our services. Celeritas Software Company employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our services. This information enables us to deliver faster service capabilities to our customers or to our affiliates and/or other sales partners, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All WinMaximizer.com or Celeritas Software Company cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to WinMaximizer.com or Celeritas Software Company, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information. Our Cookies are mainly maintained to track our affiliates and/or other sales partners to ensure proper payments for their sales and tracking activities relating to their affiliate relationship with us.

#### Links

We may offer links from our website to other third party websites which may be hosted by our co-branding partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and Celeritas Software Company makes no representation as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit.

#### Security

The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain such safeguards to protect security of servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, provide customer service, or maintain your account with us. 

#### Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you in order to reflect our practices and provide greater protection for your information. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted promptly here, so please check back periodically.

#### Acceptance of Terms

By using the Celeritas Software Company services, accessing the WinMaximizer.com web site, or purchasing Celeritas Software Company products you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use that are described in this Privacy Policy.

#### _If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at[support@WinMaximizer.com](mailto:support@WinMaximizer.com)._

#### WinMaximizer is a common-law trademark of Celeritas Software Company Inc.

* 25 system errors can be fixed using the free version of WinMaximizer. The full product can be purchased for $39.95.
